# Ricky Liew

Full Stack Web Developer

## CONTACT



Sydney, Australia



rickyliew@hotmail.com



http://rickyliew.site/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/liewricky



https://github.com/RCode-Blue

## SKILLS

JavaScript

Heroku

Python

Microsoft Azure

React

Google Cloud

Redux

Flask

Django

### EDUCATION

Web development immersive General Assembly 2018

#### PROFILE

I started out in IT operations but decided that it's more fun to make things. My career trajectory has been fun and varied, and I enjoy creating solutions that solve people's problems.

I like working with others who enjoys collaboration and learning new things.

I live in Sydney and am a lover of food and dogs. When not declaring variables, we bake way too much for us and our friends. We are also prone to creating work for ourselves by springing strays from shelters.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Full Stack Developer

CareerTrackers (Jul 2018 – May 2019)

As an early member of their newly-minted developer team, I created solutions to enable business processes across sites around the country, improved existing solutions and consulted with stakeholders to deliver projects and solutions.

- Created forms and workflows using Google Cloud Services for corporate use such as leave approval and travel approval.
- Improved existing codebase to reduce maintenance requirements.
- Learned Flask in order to create onboarding management application for new employees.

note: This is a full-time developer role, not an internship.

# Windows Infrastructure / SharePoint Administrator Channel Seven (Aug 2011 – Feb 2018)

Channel Seven (Aug 2011 – Feb 2018)

My role at Seven was primarily to take a leadership role in their new SharePoint intranet. This required collaboration with stakeholder across multiple sites and disciplines, designing the SharePoint site architecture, customisation of sites and creating solutions.

- Designed, installed and documented Production, Development and Staging environment. for the intranet SharePoint farm.
- Scripted the deployment of the above farms using PowerShell.
- Customisation of sites, including creation of web parts.
- Creating solutions, requiring development using C# and Java Script.
- Consulting with stakeholders for specific portal creation, eg: Seven Sports, Election, advertising campaigns etc